You know a detective named. uh.
Danny Kelly?
We worked homicide
at Brooklyn North together.
Is this the officer you disclosed
having a domestic relationship with?
That wasn't him.
That was someone else.
Hey.
I dated a detective.
He put me in the hospital.
And when I told my lieutenant.
everyone I worked with and grew up with.
stopped talking to me.
You fucking came back.
Marshall says "hi-ya."
Go fuck yourself. Mikey.
DOA's name is Caleb Easton.
You know this isn't an O.D.
Adrian Murado was an overdose
that came through right before I left.
It was the same thing.
Is that the girlfriend?
Yeah. From a couple neighbors'
security cameras.
-She's always hiding her face.
-Anyone ever speak to her?
She did have a tattoo. though.
It was like. uh. a little red flower.
So you think it's the girlfriend?
And you think she's a serial killer?
You're not gonna make it
out of your probationary period.
-And do you have an ID?
-I have my SNAP card.
You're safe now.
Do you have a laptop?
Is there any way I could borrow it?
Yeah.
Who's Oliver Charles?
On my computer.
you're looking up some guy.
Kind of a lot.
Fancy rich lawyer guy trying to bag.
You're jealous.
I took a picture of you.
I just need you to get
a couple more things for me.
I'm freaking out. I should not
have given you back the drugs.
-Dad?
-He's dead.
I met your dad when I was your age.
And he hurt me. Mira.
He's not a good man.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Can I tell you a secret?
Those scissors are scaring
those guys out there.
Do you think
you can give them to me?
No?
You're not ready yet.
You tell me when you're ready.
Can I put this around you
till you warm up?
That was so good.
That was amazing.
Thank you for these.
My backpack.
-What about your backpack?
-She took my backpack.
Yeah?
What did it look like?
It's red and it has pins.
a-and I want it back.
-I want it back.
-We're... we're gonna get it.
-Mira!
-Please. ma'am.
-Hey. sorry.
-Mom?
She's right in there.
I know she's right there.
-Let's go to Mom.
-Ma'am. please.
Okay?
Just let me go by.
-Look straight ahead.
-I'm serious.
-Ma'am. Ma'am. please!
-Oh. baby!
-Mom?
Oh. baby. Baby. Okay.
I've got you.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Marshall.
Hey.
Here.
Hey. Alice?
I'm Frank Choi.
C-H-O-I. Choi.
In C-20 with Nora.
-She sent me to work this with you.
-Great. looking forward to it.
You know.
this is a big one for a baby agent.
You lucked out.
Alice.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Agent Choi. this is Detective Connelly.
He's the lead on this homicide.
You two know each other already?
She dated the lead detective
for ten years.
-After you.
-Yeah.
In... in high school.
and then got back together again.
or some crazy. incestuous cop shit.
We have three bodies and a fugitive.
She's been an agent for five minutes.
I'm not... I'm not teaching
first grade here.
You can't put her on this.
She's not ready.
Look. I don't... I don't question
your leadership.
-Yeah. thank you for never questioning...
-But this is...
-this is a mistake.
-my leadership. I really appreciate it.
That's a sensational tie. Frank.
I love a deep. rich plum.
Nora. it's a mistake.
Alice?
Hey. just a minute.
Choi tells me you know
the lead detective pretty well.
You have to tell me right now
that you can handle this.
I can handle it.
Then you suck it up
and get back out there.
and you do not let Frank
take over your case.
Never done one of these before.
Police cooperation with the Feds.
joint initiative. whatever the fuck.
You ever done one?
Nope.
Be good to work together again.
-Yeah.
-Good.
Yeah.
♪ Once I believed
that when love came to me ♪
♪ It would come with rockets.
bells and poetry ♪
♪ But with me and you... ♪
-Hey.
-Hi.
Um... how... h-how are you?
Good. Yeah.
Um...
I... I got you everything
that you asked for.
and. um. I just...
I... I can't do this anymore.
So you can do whatever the fuck you want
with those pictures because...
I'm done.
Do you think you're a good person?
No.
No. I don't. I... I mean. not after this.
Wanna get high with me?
Come on.
What the fuck else
are you gonna do?
Wait.
Alright. everyone. take a seat.
This is a joint initiative with the NYPD.
Alice Black and Frank Choi
will be running point from the Bureau.
Detective Daniel Kelly is the lead
on the Caleb Easton homicide.
and Detective Marshall Connelly
for Oliver Charles.
Alice. walk us through
what we have so far.
There are three victims we know of:
Adrian Murado. Caleb Easton.
Oliver Charles.
All suspicious overdoses
with the same M.O.
The victims are connected?
Yes.
Caleb Easton is the connection point.
Caleb Easton and Oliver Charles
went to law school together
and were friends.
The connection between
Caleb Easton and Adrian Murado
is in this piece of security footage
from 2012.
Here. you can see Adrian Murado
forcefully pulling a female
out of a bodega.
Through the window.
there is a black Mercedes.
This car is registered to Caleb Easton.
The suspect is female.
White. late 20s.
no distinctive features
other than a poppy tattoo at her pelvis.
We have images of her coming and going
out of Caleb Easton
and Oliver Charles' residences.
And in the case of Caleb Easton.
she was staying there for weeks
and was described as his girlfriend.
There's no pictures of her face.
How is that possible?
She's masked in public.
She destroyed Oliver Charles'
security system.
This is deliberate.
She knows what she's doing.
We think there's a good chance
she was trafficked as a child.
So. she's been trained
since she was 12. 13 years old
to blend in. in plain sight.
That's what the traffickers teach them.
That's what they know.
Okay. so what is she after then?
Money?
How much digging
have you done into the financials?
Uh. I really believe
there is a deeper motivation here.
This is an attractive young woman
with a history of prostitution.
You don't think that she's picking up
rich guys and taking their money?
No. I... I don't.
There were no withdrawals.
There were no bank transfers.
Murado was a suspected
trafficker of underage girls.
I really think the homicides
are payback of some kind.
I... I think she's on a suicide mission.
There's nothing to back that up.
Why would she leave
Oliver Charles' daughter alive?
H-How could she be so careful
to hide herself
and then leave a living witness?
Doesn't want to kill a kid.
Or she knows people
aren't always gonna believe
what a traumatized teenager says.
If she was trafficked.
then she'd know that pretty well.
We need to talk to the daughter.
We talk to her at the scene?
Uh. she was in shock.
The suspect forced her
to cut her own hair off.
Or she could have done it herself.
She was in there
with her father's body.
Maybe she was scared or angry.
Look. none of this helps us
find her right now.
How do we... how do we find her?
Where is our killer?
We still have security footage
we need to review.
The suspect met Oliver Charles
at a party at his law firm.
Uh. she was working
for a catering company as a waitress.
so we pulled the employment records.
and. uh. we're gonna speak
to her manager.
Boom. That's good.
Let's talk to everyone
who worked that night and get a name.
Yuti. thanks for covering my shifts.
Hey. Your mama okay?
You were away so long.
Yeah.
I'm probably gonna have
to visit her again.
-But she's responding well to the chemo.
-Uh. Vanessa.
I found some stuff that belongs to you
in the mother's room.
You have a place to stay right now?
There were some bags in the closet.
I don't know what stuff
you're talking about.
Oh. okay.
Good night.
I'll see you in the morning.
Mm-hmm.
There she is.
You little slut.
Hi.
Howdy.
I didn't even know you had a mom.
No offense. you don't seem
like you have a mom.
I assumed you were made by AI
to be the woman of my dreams.
Well. I'm gonna have to go
see her again soon. so.
Oh. bullshit.
I know when you're lying.
You've been wiping my ass
for three years.
Maybe one day.
you'll let me wipe yours.
Anytime you want.
Mm!
You'd be fine if I leave.
For real.
Where'd you really go?
I blame my mom for this.
She hired you and died right after.
But I'm stuck with you.
-And the worst part.
-Mm-hmm?
You're not even a real nurse.
You wanna pay for a real nurse?
Fuck that.
I missed you.
Hey. you promised I'd get something
when you got back.
What do you mean?
Need some help there?
You're so beautiful.
This is my gift to you.
You want anything else?
You pay.
But you're priceless.
Hey.
What's going on?
Jinny Allen.
-The ID from the catering company?
-Yeah.
They found a Jinny Allen
who fits the age and height.
who checked into a homeless shelter
earlier tonight.
Ooh.
Choi's getting on his cool jacket.
You guys got a gift shop or something
where I can get one of those?
Hang on.
I'm gonna grab a fizzy water.
Yo. anyone else want something?
-Danny. you coming?
-Anyone?
Uh. nah. I... I can't kick down doors.
I got the fucking sciatica.
So. she checked into a shelter?
-Uh-huh.
-Using her real name?
Yeah. she checked into
a traceable public place
using her real name.
Sounds like we got her.
Can we just go home?
Okay. Let's go.
-You get the door?
-Yep.
Hold it.
We gotta talk to the daughter.
Go get the mom to say yes
to an interview.
-You're good at that.
-What am I good at?
Getting scared women
to fall in love with you.
Yeah?
Remember when I broke
your blue coffee mug?
I was so scared you'd be mad.
And what did you say to me?
God damn it. you broke my mug.
And it was magical.
Alright. I'll text you.
Come on.
Tell me something about you.
Why do you always make me
do all the talking?
Because you never shut up.
Yeah.
Are you having significant
breakthrough pain?
Yes. nurse.
I'm having significant
breakthrough pain.
Okay.
I never feel it when you do it.
Good night.
Sweet Vanessa.
♪ Yellow diamonds in the light ♪
♪ I was standing side by side ♪
♪ As your shadow crosses mine ♪
♪ What it takes to come alive ♪
♪ It's the way I'm feeling ♪
♪ I just can't deny ♪
♪ But I've gotta let it go ♪
♪ We found love
in a hopeless place ♪
♪ We found love in a hopeless place ♪
♪ We found love
in a hopeless place ♪
♪ We found love in a hopeless place ♪
Mm.
This cookie is so big!
Yeah. that is a big cookie.
Pay in coin.
Coins? Yeah. okay.
You've gotta work at it.
It's not going to happen overnight.
You're going to have days
where you don't know if you can go on.
But I'm here to tell you. girl.
you got this.
I got this.
You keep doing these exercises.
these affirmations.
Say it back to me.
I can create the life I want to have.
I can create the life I wanna have.
I give myself permission to accept
exactly where I am in this moment.
I am safe and in the present.
My presence alone
will bring someone joy today.
I have survived every day
before this one.
I am safe and in the present.
I am safe...
and in the present.
And in the present.
I am safe and in the present.
I am safe.
I am safe and in the pres...
-No luck?
-Wasn't her.
Wrong Jinny Allen.
She was in holding
on drunk and disorderly
one of the days the suspect
was at Oliver Charles.
And she puked on us.
-Yeah.
-Mm.
Yep.
Good. Thank you.
You got something
off the bank accounts?
Nope.
But there was a woman who was staying
at a domestic violence shelter
until about a week ago.
registered under the name Jinny Allen.
Why didn't we have that information?
Caleb Easton's sister
said that the suspect
was just getting out
of an abusive relationship.
so I've been calling DV shelters.
Those places are anonymous.
but I have some contacts
-from homicide. and I've been calling...
-Good. Yes.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-Okay.
Ma'am. we're just asking
-for a few minutes.
-She's not here anymore.
-I said it on the phone.
-Ma'am. Ma'am.
-The longer... ma'am.
-This is not what we discussed.
-Stop calling me ma'am!
-Sarah?
Sarah. this is what's going to happen.
We are going to need to interview
everyone who spoke to her.
-Oh. these women are terrified.
-I know.
But it's just gonna be me
and these two guys. okay?
Okay.
So who can we see first?
Maddie.
You... you slept next to Jinny.
You wanna go first?
I didn't really talk to her much.
I don't know what to say.
Honey. they're just
gonna ask you a few questions.
Can you. um...
I-I'm gonna get some water.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Choi told me to come check on you.
He likes you more than me.
Yeah. sorry. I just. um...
An employee. uh. Becky Lydgate.
might have been having
an affair with Jinny
and she hasn't been to work
for a few days.
We might have got something.
You good?
Did I ever do that to you?
What?
Hit me in the face?
Yeah. Marshall.
You hit me in the face.
-You don't remember?
-I don't know.
Um. I don't know.
I feel like I remember...
pieces of it.
I was just drinking a lot. and then...
you were gone. so.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I hurt you like that.
I'm really sorry.
-I gotta go.
-Wait. hey. Alice. Alice.
They're moving my mom
out of the hospital back home
'cause they don't know how long. uh...
This is gonna seem...
I don't know. I just...
would you come see her?
Please?
You were like her kid all those years.
like her daughter.
And she never stopped
thinking of you like that.
So...
Please.
I love you.
I still love you.
I don't wanna talk about that.
I...
Hey.
Becky Lydgate.
We located her cellphone.
Come on.
Hey. Is the Big Man here tonight?
I lost my phone. so.
Seven.
-I'm calling him.
-Okay. Cool.
Yo. Catherine.
Elena. can we talk?
Girl. what?
Hey. this is my sister's friend.
-so y'all gotta be extra nice.
-Hey.
Stop staring at the blog
and help me get to the trees.
We got nuggets.
Come on.
-You gotta get that protein.
-Hey. hey. hey.
I saw your message on OnlyFans.
Yeah!
I'm getting some money.
Why did you leave that family?
I told you. they fucking sucked.
You gotta cam in five minutes. bro.
-I can do both.
-No. you can't.
I'm gonna turn this fucking farm
-into an empty...
-You like my fit?
Elena. hey. No. no. Come on.
-Stop that. Stop. Stop.
-No. don't do that. Don't do that.
You told me you weren't coming back here.
okay. we talked about it.
-No.
-Let's go. Stop. Come with me right now.
You're crazy.
I know. I know. I know.
We're gonna leave.
and you're gonna come stay with me.
No.
We tried that.
You didn't have a place to stay.
And you got so sad and weird.
I know.
But I'm getting better.
Okay. if you won't leave with me.
will you take this backpack? Yeah?
It. um...
It has a toothbrush. toothpaste.
soap. uh. condoms. a sweatshirt.
And. um...
I hid some money
in this scrunchie.
Yeah. You gotta keep eating.
-And you gotta stay warm.
-I'm fine.
I'm gonna work. save up. and get a place.
It's different now.
I split my shit 50-50 with him.
What are you. a health aide?
That's what I'm gonna be.
-as soon as I'm not broke as shit.
-Hey. hey. hey.
She didn't want this for you.
Who?
Isabel?
She didn't want you to do what we did.
But where is she?
You said you were going to find her.
You said you were going
to find my sister.
Yeah. you're lying.
Pretending like she's still alive.
You know she's dead.
-I'm not a fucking baby!
-Hey.
Hey!
-Who's in there? Hey!
-Go on. you guys. Go. go. go.
-What the fuck is going on?
-Hey.
Why are they telling me
some girl came up?
Chill out. it... it's nothing.
-Whose fucking backpack is this?
-It's mine.
You lying to me?
You think this is a fucking game?!
-I'm sorry. Stop! Aah!
-Stop lying to me!
Catherine.
-Get your ass up!
-I'm sorry! It's mine. it's mine!
Please. please!
She's under the bed.
-Hey. what the fuck?
-Run! Run!
Get back here. bitch!
Who the fuck you think you are?
Pardon me.
This way.
The M.O. is different on this one.
There are multiple needle marks.
like she didn't want
to go through with it.
What. you're just gonna jump right in?
-You're not gonna say hi or anything?
-Why... why would she leave
the daughter alive but kill this woman?
-Al. Al.
-I want to talk to the daughter.
I want to know what they talked about.
what she was thinking...
Al.
Mira's gonna talk to us.
That's why I came to get you.
Okay.
How long do I have?
I don't know.
I said you were fucking good at that!
-Well...
-You are fucking good at that.
Yeah. well. you know.
You never come in here.
This all your stuff?
Cool.
What's with the. uh...
Why do you have all these photos
of these guys?
They. um...
How much are you...
scamming them for?
A lot.
Fuck yeah.
How 'bout I take the day shift?
Let Yuti go home. get some rest?
Whatever you like.
Love the hair.
Oh.
Thank you.
What's she going to remember?
Almost nothing.
Her memory will be in pieces.
The trauma will make half
of what happened just disappear.
It's called memory distortion.
and it's not gonna make any sense.
so don't ask her to explain.
Her family is just falling apart.
so you have to become that for her.
Be her mom.
You had a mom. right?
Oh. no.
Tell me you had a fucking mom.
You mind if I take some notes?
How are you feeling?
I feel good. I feel fine.
Most of it I don't even remember.
So. what is the last thing...
you do remember?
I mean. nothing.
Really.
I don't remember her face...
or anything about her.
And she told me that he was sick.
Who?
I don't remember.
Was it your dad?
I don't know.
Do you remember
anything about her?
-No.
-Hey.
It's okay. honey.
She doesn't remember.
So try to think.
Do you remember
anything about her?
It doesn't have to be her face.
Her hands.
Her smell.
The sound of her voice.
Anything.
No.
Except that she couldn't feel
her fingertips.
Because...
we did our hair like twins.
And she touched my curling iron
and didn't even feel it.
Why couldn't she feel her fingertips?
Um. she said that she got hurt
when she was my age.
Um. my retainer was in my backpack.
Is it gone?
I haven't been wearing it.
Are you mad?
-No.
-Come on.
Get back to her face.
She talked to you
about when she was young.
What did she say?
My dad had. um...
My dad had sex with her
when she was my age.
He paid her.
Ho!
I'm here.
Is there any way...
would you consider
speaking to a sketch artist?
No. I don't remember.
I don't remember her face.
Bullshit.
How can she not remember the face?
-I think you can.
-I got you.
Okay?
But she didn't kill me.
-No. I know.
-Why?
-I know.
-Why didn't she kill you?
I don't know why.
Why didn't she kill you?
I don't know.
Why do you think she didn't kill you?
This has to stop. okay?
I'm not your mom.
So I'm not gonna treat you
like a child.
I saw you holding those scissors.
I know you're strong enough to do this.
Um. she...
She wanted me to give you this.
She said to give it to the police.
Hey. Hey.
Hey. I got you.
Hey. you did so good.
I'm so proud of you.
No more.
Okay.
You think it's time you cleaned out
your mom's room?
She can't use it anymore.
She isn't coming back.
But I'm here.
And I could really use a place to stay.
Yeah. That makes sense.
And I'm gonna use your car.
Okay.
Good.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Tell 'em what?
Exactly.
Okay. so that's Oliver Charles.
Caleb Easton.
And that's Jay Easton.
But who's that?
Who's the teenager
sitting on Jay Easton's lap?
Jesus.
I ran the face through
Child Protective Services
and there's a match.
Isabel Luna.
The facial recognition is not 100%
because she's under the age of three
in the photo.
but I think it's her.
Isabel Luna entered the system in 1998.
A foster care placement after abandonment.
All the records for her stop
after the age of 15 in 2012.
And there's one more person.
That girl?
That's her.
This is who we're looking for.
-We don't know that.
-This girl is wearing the same dress
that the suspect is wearing
in the bodega.
This photo could have been taken
the night before. Look.
I think it's a distraction.
-A distraction?
-We're doing what she wants us to do.
We're... we're asking questions about
Jay Easton instead of going after her.
You don't think that's relevant?
That she was doing this with these men
when she was a child?
-I didn't say it wasn't relevant.
-Alright.
-Did you hear that? Did I say...
-Alright. Alright.
Maybe the focus
should be on Jay Easton.
Maybe we should all start asking
why he's in a photo partying
with two underage girls.
Look. it's been a long day.
Go home for a few hours. rest up.
Well done.
You were really good in there.
I just forgot how good you are.
Here.
Hi.
Co... uh. come on in.
She's gonna be so excited to see you.
Mom?
Hey. you awake?
I got somebody here to see you.
You came.
Thank you.
Oh. I got you.
I've got you.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
Hel... hello.
I'll have the salad.
This salad is... is delicious.
Marta! Hey. you're back.
Sorry. I'm out on a jog so I can't type.
Um. listen. I want to see you.
I want to finally meet you.
So let me take you out
for some light bites.
Oh. my God. did I just say "light bites"?
Um. alright. just. just.
just call me back. okay. because
I feel like we could be soul mates.
Are we soul mates?
Hi!
I'm Marta Dreznick. and I love salad.
What was I like?
When?
When you met me.
When I was a kid.
You weren't a kid.
You were never a kid.
Even when you were young...
you seemed so old.
Like you'd seen too much.
And you were cold.
Like a robot.
No feelings.
You can be like that. you know.
I taught you how to feel things.
To care about people the way
I cared about you.
-You need a rest?
-Uh-uh.
-I can come back.
-Your mom left you.
And I let you come over every day.
I fed you dinner.
And I helped you
with your homework.
I know.
But you didn't learn a fucking thing.
You're still so cold.
And now. you're gonna ruin
my son's career.
And you don't care.
Do you think he'll ever get promoted
if there's rumors out there
that he hurts you?
You're a brick on him!
So you need to fix it.
-You need to tell the truth.
-What?
You tell the truth.
that he was drinking too much
and you had a bad breakup.
Now. that's the truth.
I know you.
I know who you really are.
You hear me?
-Take it back! Take it all back!
-Mom!
-It didn't happen! It didn't happen!
-Hey! Mom! You gotta stop.
-Stop! Alice. Alice!
-It didn't happen! It didn't happen!
-Alice. Alice.
-I never reported any of it.
even when I had to miss work
to go to the hospital.
I wanted to be the one to explain.
Please. I'm sorry.
Alice. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. She is not that...
her emotions are all over the place.
She just wants to know
that I am gonna be okay.
and she wants you to know
that I've changed. alright?
-That I'm changing a lot of my life...
-You changed things? What did you change?
You got a new coat? What?
-You got new pants? New haircut?
-Please stop for a second.
Stop making jokes.
Okay?
I know that it's not...
I've stopped drinking.
I'm sober.
And every day. I'm trying to figure out
how I fucked this up.
How do I get back?
How do I come back from this?
Like. is there... is there ever
a way that you can...
What?
Forgive you?
Yeah. Yes.
I miss touching
the back of your neck.
Oh. yeah.
I liked putting my face in it.
My whole... whole face.
What I wanted to ask you
is if there's a way that we can...
a different way
that we can talk about. um...
what happened.
'Cause the rumors
aren't good for anything.
Right?
I just want... I just... like.
could you call my lieutenant
and say that you're okay.
and that I'm okay to move up?
Because then. it's just us.
It's just us.
Then. we can just talk
and... and work it out. you know?
Just tell me how to make this better.
I gotta get back now.
I'm not calling your lieutenant.
Hey. Hey.
What happened with you and Danny. huh?
Why didn't you two just fuck?
You know what hurt the most?
I was watching you suffer
through being stuck with me
while you were in love with somebody else.
being a good person every fucking day!
Go back in the house.
Jesus.
Okay.
You're going to have days
where you don't know if you can go on.
But I'm here to tell you. girl.
-you got this.
-I got this.
You keep doing these exercises.
these affirmations...
Say it back to me.
I can create the life I want to have.
I give myself permission to accept
exactly where I am in this moment.
I am safe and in the present.
My presence alone
will bring someone joy today.
I have survived every day
before this one.
I am safe and in the present.
I am safe and in the present
I do not need to be perfect
to be loved.
I am worthy of love and compassion.
especially for myself.
My needs. feelings. and emotions
are valid.
I am enough exactly as I am.
I do not need to be perfect
to be loved.
I am free to love what I love.
My heart is my strongest weapon.
I have survived every day
before this one.
I can create the life I want to have.
I give myself permission to accept
exactly where I am in this moment.
I am safe and in the present.
My presence alone
will bring someone joy today.
Now. visualize your future
and walk towards it.
And please remember
to like. comment. and subscribe.
She's out there somewhere.
this avenging angel.
our murderess.
You have no idea who you're dealing with
and you are gonna end up dead.
I don't care if I die.
And you pulled your gun
on your ex-boyfriend.
We are one conversation away
from you losing your job.
You're a liability.
Anything you do to him.
they'll use it against you.
Hey.
What's the punishment for people
who know what's happening
and do nothing?
Listen to me. I can help you!
If you have anything
that you wanna tell me.
you better tell me now.
I need to know we're all on the same page
about this investigation.
Nora's hiding something.
Her name is on the report!
She's here.
Hey.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm